{
    "id": "c65cdf8dd91b4cfc90b3ee6ae2983159",
    "title": "Present Participle Or Past Participle",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The film was so …………………… that I fell asleep in the middle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boring",
                "bored"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11cfaba160be4c989afce55c423c158f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you like to come over? I’m so ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boring",
                "bored"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9bdac9edbc946dc872ff4b4ac61402c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The journey was quite ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tiring",
                "tired"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "740e5cd06be94db680795300d0b8f97b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her behavior was quite …………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "disgusting",
                "disgusted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b500f0c4a7774473a487eef3eedba9b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She left in a hurry because she was …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "disgusting",
                "disgusted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e3ff9a466e445fa9878d8948766aa8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………. everyone by turning up late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "annoyed",
                "annoying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3bc6cdc459054be786253ee5811e79d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was really …………………. by her story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inspired",
                "inspiring"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96bec319ff34424388bce774eea0f5b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her story was so …………………….. that they decided to publish it as a book.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inspiring",
                "inspired"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9d142db207349f9aaf7d6aa1606d0c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was very ……………………… with his results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pleased",
                "pleasing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "978c3cdaad98439d9abca8fe87a92b41"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were …………………… to hear that there had been an accident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shocked",
                "shocking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c14b15e1433a4e51af556f215d05501c"
        }
    ]
}